Let me also show you how to set up
recurring actions your AI assistant can
run automatically by using something
called cron jobs. Let's go back to the
open claw control panel. And then on the
left hand side, go into cron jobs.
And on this screen, you'll have two main
boxes. On the left, this box is just the
status. You'll see if theuler is
enabled, how many jobs you have, and the
next time it's going to wake up. And on
the right is where you create a job.
Let's start by giving our job a name.
I'll name this summarize emails and
meetings. You can add a description if
you want to. Next, let's go down to the
schedule. Right now, it's set for every
30 minutes. So, for example, I could
change this to 1 and then from minutes
to days. And lastly, we need to tell the
AI what this job is. That's what you put
into the system text box here. So, I'll
type check my Gmail and Google calendar.
Summarize anything important since the
last run. Then, send me a short update
on Telegram. So, now with this job, for
every single day, it's going to
summarize my Gmail in Google Calendar,
and that's going to send me a message on
Telegram with anything important. Once
you're happy with this, just click on
add job.
And then you'll see that new job down
here. And that's it. Your assistant is
now going to run this job automatically
on the schedule that you chose. And once
you get the hang of this, you can
schedule basically anything. If it's a
task that you want your assistant to
handle automatically, just turn it into
a job